{
    "subject": "Emilio_Fern\u00e1ndez",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "R\u00edo_Escondido__1948_film_",
    "human_readable": "Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed the film R\u00edo Escondido (1948).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9239826798439026,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9178003668785095,
            "question": "Is Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8984825611114502,
            "question": "Who directed the film R\u00edo Escondido?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7838083505630493,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6964648365974426,
            "question": "What year was the film R\u00edo Escondido released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5687604546546936,
            "question": "Can you find information about the plot of R\u00edo Escondido?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5320534110069275,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in a film titled R\u00edo Escondido?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5230781435966492,
            "question": "What impact did Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez have on Mexican cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5166656374931335,
            "question": "Where was the film R\u00edo Escondido likely filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5099280476570129,
            "question": "What genre might the film R\u00edo Escondido belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed the film R\u00edo Escondido (1948).",
            "html": "yago_9210_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the film R\u00edo Escondido likely filmed?",
            "html": "yago_9210_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez have on Mexican cinema?",
            "html": "yago_9210_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes might be explored in a film titled R\u00edo Escondido?",
            "html": "yago_9210_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9210_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9210_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9210_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9210_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9210_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9210_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9210_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9210_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9210_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9210_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain several references to Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez's involvement with the film R\u00edo Escondido, including:\n\n* A line from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9210/re-ranker-msmarco/77.txt that reads \"R\u00edo Escondido (1947, dir.  Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez) \u2013 Director, screenwriter\".\n* Another line from the same file_path that reads \"The Fugitive (1947, dirs.  John Ford, Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez) \u2013 Co-Director\", which implies that Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez was also involved in the production of The Fugitive, a film that shares a similar title with one of the works listed under R\u00edo Escondido.\n* A mention of Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez as the director of R\u00edo Escondido (1948) in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9210/re-ranker-msmarco/31.txt.\n\nAll these references collectively suggest that Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez was indeed involved with the film R\u00edo Escondido, and directed it."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents clearly states that Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed the film \"R\u00edo Escondido\" in 1948, supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}